[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which pokémon evolves into Charmeleon?",
        "options": ["Charmander", "Charizard", "Bulbasaur", "Pikachu", "Squirtle"],
        "answer": "Charmander",
        "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which pokémon evolves into Grovyle?",
        "options": ["Turtwig", "Treecko", "Bulbasaur", "Snivy", "Chikorita"],
        "answer": "Treecko",
        "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is the color of a male Magikarp's mustache?",
        "options": ["Blue", "Red", "Green", "Yellow", "White"],
        "answer": "Yellow",
        "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is the Johto PokéDex number of Gyarados?",
        "options": ["#130", "#77", "#129", "#175", "#222"],
        "answer": "#77",
        "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which move Electabuzz cannot know?",
        "options": ["Thunder Punch", "Meditate", "Ice Punch", "Thunder Fang", "Thunder Shock"],
        "answer": "Thunder Fang",
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What is the base Special Attack points of Gengar?",
        "options": ["135", "130", "125", "120", "110"],
        "answer": "130",
        "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What is the natural enemy of Zangoose?",
        "options": ["Zigzagoon", "Arbok", "Ekans", "Seviper", "Serperior"],
        "answer": "Seviper",
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which Pokémon is not Grass type?",
        "options": ["Parasect", "Skiploom", "Lileep", "Ferroseed", "Sudowoodo"],
        "answer": "Sudowoodo",
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which Pokémon is not Dragon type?",
        "options": ["Kingdra", "Vibrava", "Altaria", "Fraxure", "Charizard"],
        "answer": "Charizard",
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which Pokémon is not Dragon type?",
        "options": ["Mega Gyarados", "Mega Ampharos", "Mega Altaria", "Mega Charizard X", "Mega Sceptile"],
        "answer": "Mega Gyarados",
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which Pokémon has the highest speed base?",
        "options": ["Scyther", "Rapidash", "Dugtrio", "Charizard", "Gengar"],
        "answer": "Dugtrio",
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "What is the specialty of Johto's fifth Gym Leader? The leader is Chuck",
        "options": ["Bug Type Pokémon", "Fighting Type Pokémon", "Normal Type Pokémon", "Dragon Type Pokémon", "Fire Type Pokémon"],
        "answer": "Fighting Type Pokémon",
        "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Deerling evolves into",
        "options": ["Stantler", "Virizion", "Sawsbuck", "Girafarig", "Absol"],
        "answer": "Sawsbuck",
        "difficulty": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Which Pokémon is dual typed?",
        "options": ["Gigalith", "Tangrowth", "Conkeldurr", "Wigglytuff", "Alomomola"],
        "answer": "Wigglytuff",
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Which Pokémon is not from Unova",
        "options": ["Woobat", "Munna", "Burmy", "Tympole", "Leavanny"],
        "answer": "Burmy",
        "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Which Pokémon is not from Sinnoh",
        "options": ["Mothim", "Bibarel", "Kricketot", "Shieldon", "Throh"],
        "answer": "Throh",
        "difficulty": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Which Pokémon does not evolve when traded?",
        "options": ["Haunter", "Machoke", "Electabuzz", "Magneton", "Graveler"],
        "answer": "Magneton",
        "difficulty": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Which Pokémon is exclusively fire type?",
        "options": ["Combusken", "Monferno", "Quilava", "Pignite", "Litleo"],
        "answer": "Quilava",
        "difficulty": 2
    }
]
